# KIT SITOU

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

619-832-5741

linkedin.com/in/kitisitou

San Diego, CA

#### EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS National University, CA Jul 2022

ASSOCIATE IN GENERAL STUDIES Columbia College, MO May 2015

#### SKILLS

Can be obtain secret clearance
Have driver License
Problem solving.
Inventory Management
Customer Service
Project management
Attention to detail.
Time management
Verbal communication
Strategic planning
Bilingual

#### EXPERTISE

Windows OS/Mac OS
Hardware/Software
Repair
Network Configuration
SCCM
Account Management
Asset management
ServiceNow
Microsoft 365/ OneDrive
Lucid Chart
Sharepoint

#### PROFILE

I am a 10-year Navy veteran. And have 5 years of IT experience. Working with Illumina as a Desktop Level IV Technician has focused on IT asset management since Sep 2021. I was also a Level II field tech at Peraton, assisting with technical issues throughout San Diego County.

I worked in the Micro repair department; I was responsible for solving daily trouble tickets, repairing and imaging hardware, and providing remote desktop support. Repair printers, patch, and fix network-related issues. I have troubleshooting experience with hardware, software, and servers.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# IT Asset Management| Desktop Level IV Technician Illumina

2022-Current

- Provide consulting on technology to the department for over 150k procurement.
- Managing the ServiceNow Queue for Hardware Requests.
- Conducts quarterly inventory audits of over 2700 assets.
- managing the procurement, deployment, maintenance, and disposal or reclamation of hardware assets such as computers, servers, network gear, smartphones, and other electronic devices
- Maintain CMDB accuracy of critical asset CI data.
- Monitor all renewals, new hardware purchases, research, and guidance for internal users.
- Assists in developing and implementing asset lifecycle procedures for managing hardware assets.
- Ensuring compliance with established regulations and maximizing the company's resources and policies.
- PC Imaging using any tools such as SCCM Autopilot.
- Skills: ServiceNow · SAP Ariba · Microsoft Excel · Inventory Analysis · IT Procurement · Presentation Skills · Quote Preparation

#### **Level II Field Tech**

Peraton 2020-2022

- Diagnosed and troubleshot technical issues, repairing and restoring equipment, including laptops, desktops, printers, and scanners throughout San Diego County.
- Managed and documented communication using ServiceNow.
- Supported over 600 Tier 2 tickets, reduced tickets to lower 30+ ranges, and maintained SLA level.
- Led In-Place Upgrade team in delivering Windows 10 Deployment, resulting in a complete Windows 10 Environment.
- Order repair parts and communicate with vendors.
- Support deployment and de-commission of servers.

# KIT SITOU

# EXPERIENCE (CONT.)

#### CONTACT

619-832-5741

linkedin.com/in/kitisitou

San Diego, CA

# HOBBIES

Photography
Dance
Music Composition
Video editing
Blogging

# OTHER SKILLS

Graphic design
Writing and Editing
Marketing
SEO
MailChimp
CovertKit
Canva
Google Analytic

# COMPLETED PROJECT

Annual Computer refresh
Website development
WordPress
Shopify
Amazon seller central
Amazon Ads
management
Facebook Ads
management
Google Ads management
After Effects
Final Cut Pro
Microsoft Office

# **Information System Technician**

Naval Medical Center U.S. Navy

2019-2020

- Led 4 Sailors in supporting 883 users, responding to 593 trouble tickets.
- Maintaining and repairing hardware and software. I managed over \$116k in procurement and lifecycle replacement of 425 computers.
- Upgraded all old computer OS, which increased 24/7 Defense Cyberspace Operations mission capability and ensured 99% system availability.
- Configuring computer networks. Repairing, troubleshooting, and providing technical support on-site or via phone or email.
- Install and configure over 515 networks and provide internet access to users.

# **Maintenance Manager**

USS Bonhomme Richard | U.S. Navy

2018-2019

- USS Bonhomme Richard was docking for shipboard repairment, and I was responsible for planning, organizing, and conducting all related equipment repairs.
- I was the sole communicator with other contractors when planning equipment load and offload.
- Conducted and oversaw daily task assignments for junior sailors for shipboard repair.
- Onload and offload 200-line items valued over 30K, transport items to other ships.

# **Warehouse Manager**

USS Bonhomme Richard | U.S. Navy

Feb2018-Nov2018

- As warehouse manager in the food service division, I procured and maintained over 1 million worth of food items on board.
- I was also responsible for inventory adjustment and recorded daily usage using the Food Service Management System.
- Planned and coordinated 12 food stores on loads operation, including inport and underway replenishments.
- Managed and conducted 14 weekly spot inventories to improve the storeroom's 96% accuracy and audit for over 765 line items.
- Led 7 Culinary Specialists, 10 Food Service Attendants, and 10 Marines in providing 7,000 nutritious meals daily.

## **Food Service Manager**

Naval Base San Diego | U.S. Navy

2017-2018

- As Food Service Manager, I was responsible for the daily operations of restaurants and other food service establishments.
- I operate the establishment's human resource and administrative functions: planning menus, training, discipline, scheduling, and motivated employees.
- Managed 21 military and civilian personnel in daily operations by providing over 1,500 quality meals.
- Provided service and supported over 214 tenants and 800 Midshipmen. Determined and installed appropriate security measures.

# KIT SITOU

IT ASSET SPECIAST

#### CONTACT

619-832-5741

ctwohofa@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/kitisitou

San Diego, CA

DESIRED EMPLOYMENT STATE/CITY\*

SAN DIEGO, CA (can be relocated)

# LANGUAGE

English Chinese mandarin Cantonese

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELPMENT

- Professional Presentation Skills
   SkillPath | San Diego | 12June2016
   Effective business presentations.
- Information Assurance Policy & Technology
   Department of defense | Lemoore | 2Mar2016
   Program of enhancing awareness related to cyber security.

#### PROFESSIONAL ACHIEVEMENT

- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal 12 JUL 2019
- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal | 25 FEB 2019
- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal 29 NOV 2017
- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal | 12 DEC 2014
- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal | 14 NOV 2012
- Letter of Appreciation | 2018
- Letter of Appreciation 2015